Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection of Government Publications PE.045
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: State Government Publications, 1909-1982
  - New York: Committee on the Education and Employment of Women, 1964 (Box 10)
  - New York (constitution), 1936 (Box 10)
  - New York: Department of Labor, 1913-1914, 1926 (Box 10)
  - New York: Department of Labor, 1930-1939 (Box 10)
  - New York: Department of Labor, 1940-1949 (Box 10)
  - New York: Department of Labor, 1960-1969 (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Labor, 1982 (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Labor: Board of Mediation, undated (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Labor: Division of Employment, 1964 (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Labor: Division of Employment, 1966 (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Labor: Division of Industrial Relations, 1946, undated (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Labor: Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance, 1939 (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Labor: Division of Research and Statistics, 1968-1973 (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Labor: Division of Women, 1939, 1941 (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Labor: Division of Women in Industry and Minimum Wage, 1920-1943 (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Labor: Industrial Board, 1913 (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Labor: Women's Commission, 1943 (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Education, 1949 (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Farms and Markets, 1920 (Box 11)
  - New York: Department of Social Welfare, 1958 (Box 11)
  - New York: Food Investigating Commission, 1912 (Box 11)
  - New York: Governor's Commission on Unemployment Relief, 1936 (Box 11)
  - New York: Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions, 1940 (Box 11)
  - New York: Labor Relations Board, 1940 (Box 11)
  - New York: Public Employment Relations Board (Taylor Law), circa 1968 (Box 11)
  - New York: Manpower Advisory Council, 1966 (Box 11)
  - New York: Standing Committee on Labor, 1984 (Box 11)
  - New York: War Council Committee on Discrimination in Employment, 1942 (Box 11)
  - New York: Workmen's Compensation Board, 1944, 1949 (Box 11)
  - New York: Workmen's Compensation Board, 1957-1964 (Box 11)
  - North Dakota: Industrial Commission, 1921 (Box 11)
  - North Dakota: Workmen's Compensation Board, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Oklahoma: Department of Labor, 1953 (Box 11)
  - Oklahoma: Employment Service, 1953-1954 (Box 11)
  - Oregon: Bureau of Labor: Research and Information Division, undated (Box 11)
  - Oregon: Department of Employment, 1959, 1965 (Box 11)
  - Oregon: State Employment Service, 1957 (Box 11)
  - Oregon: Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1957 (Box 11)
  - Pennsylvania: Labor and Industry Department, 1919-1940 (Box 11)
  - Pennsylvania: Labor Relations Board, 1937 (Box 11)
  - Pennsylvania: Fair Employment Practice Commission, 1955-1956 (Box 11)
  - Pennsylvania: Works Progress Administration, 1936, 1940 (Box 11)
  - Puerto Rico: Department of Labor, 1960 (Box 12)
  - Puerto Rico: Department of Labor, 1957-1959 (Box 12)
  - Texas: Bureau of Labor Statistics, undated (Box 12)
  - Utah: Department of Employment Security, 1956 (Box 12)
  - Washington: Employment Security Department, 1956 (Box 12)
  - West Virginia: Department of Employment Security, 1956, 1963 (Box 12)
  - Wisconsin: Board of Public Affairs, 1912 (Box 12)
  - Wisconsin: Bureau of Labor and Industrial Statistics, 1909 (Box 12)
  - Wisconsin: Industrial Commission, 1913-1955 (Box 12)
- Series IV: Municipal Government Publications, 1903-1962
  - Bridgeport, CT, 1951 (Box 12)
  - Chicago, IL: Mayor's Committee on Race Relations, 1944 (Box 12)
  - Detroit, MI: Mayor's Committee on Race Relations, 1926 (Box 12)
  - Milwaukee, WI: Common Council (report), 1927, 1929 (Box 12)
  - New York, NY: Board of Estimate and Apportionment, 1917 (Box 12)
  - New York, NY: Board of Higher Education, 1956 (Box 12)
  - New York, NY: Bureau of Labor Standards, undated (Box 12)
  - New York, NY: Department of Labor, 1957, 1962 (Box 12)
  - New York, NY: Emergency Relief Bureau, 1937 (Box 12)
  - New York, NY: Mayor's Committee on National Defense, 1917 (Box 12)
  - New York, NY: Mayor's Committee on Unemployment, 1915 (Box 12)
  - New York, NY: Office of Collective Bargaining, undated (Box 12)
  - New York, NY (registered voters list), 1912 (Box 12)
  - New York, NY: Works Progress Administration I, 1938-1939 (Box 12)
  - New York, NY: Works Progress Administration II, 1938-1939 (Box 12)
  - Woolwich, England (unemployment), 1903 (Box 12)